I seek the wild places of the world to
come here to reflect and think and clear
my mind and be in away from the noise
and hustle and bustle of the concrete
jungle and all the propaganda that's
been dumped into my head since I was old
enough to understand and I'm sitting up
here Wild and Free as I can
be and I thought about living in America
man and the list of things you cannot do
without asking the government's
permission Andor paying the money you
can't be born you can't die you can't
leave things to your children you can't
own a business you can't own a home you
can't own a car you can't even fix your
house you can't teach your children what
you want to you can't collect rainwater
you can't catch a fish in this Lake you
can't shoot a deer in those woods the
government owns everything in Richmond
County Georgia they're charging people
to park their own boats in their own
yards and guys I just wonder when is
enough enough of this [__] you know
freedoms are taken away slowly and
silently and if you ever want to make a
stand we're going to have to do it
together I've had it up to my earballs
with this and I have to hike 4,000 ft up
a mountain just to be wild and free and
there's a problem with that if I have to
do that to exist in America to feel like
I'm okay and nobody's holding their
thumb over me we have a problem in this
country that we need to
address who's with
me [__]